Guide to the Larry LaRocco Collection 1982-1994
Boise State University Library, Special Collections and Archives
- General files, 1
  - University of Idaho: Transportation Study, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Upper Yaak Lawsuit, 1991-1993 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    Timber Salvage; Montana--Forest Reserves; Forest Health
  - Valbois Proposal, 1991-1993 (Box 46, Folder 30)
    Cascade, Idaho; Idaho--Resorts
  - Vasquez, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 31)
    Veterans Administration; Disabled American Veterans
    Vasquez, Robert
  - Veterans, 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 32)
    American Legion of Idaho; Health and Human Services; Veterans Administration
    H.R.2824
  - Veterans, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Veterans Affairs; Agent Orange; Veterans Administration
    Penny, Timothy J.
  - Veterans, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Veterans Administration, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Veterans Affairs; Rural Health Care
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars Speech Contest, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Schwandts, Lori
  - Vietnam, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Vietnam Veterans, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    Prisoners of War
  - Violence Against Women Act, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    Domestic Violence; Rape
    H.R.1502; S.15
  - Vitamin Supplements, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    Food and Drug Administration
  - Volunteers in Overseas Cooperative Assistance, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Wallace Gambling Raid, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    Wallace, Idaho
  - War on West, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    Clearwater Resource Coalition; Save the Western Ways Rally; Boise, Idaho; Land Use; Public Lands; West--Mythology; Grazing; Water Rights
    Craig, Larry; Babbitt, Bruce
  - War Powers, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    War and Emergencies Powers
  - Washington DC Gun Liability Law, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    Semi-Automatic Weapons; Gun Control
    Kelly, Shelly Pratt
  - Waste Isolation Pilot Plant, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Water, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    Safe Water Drinking Act
  - Water Quality, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Water Regulations, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    Idaho--Water Resources; Irrigation
  - Water Rights, 1992-1994 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    Snake River; Droughts; NAFTA
    Kempthorne, Dirk; Stallings, Richard
  - Water Spreading, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    Water Resources; Irrigation; Grazing; Bureau of Reclamation
  - Watershed, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    Watershed Management; Forest Health
    Fleischman, Joyce N.
  - Watershed, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Watershed: Henry's Fork, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    Henry's Fork Foundation; Sediment Studies; Henry's Fork of the Snake River; Forest Health
  - Weapons Systems, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Welfare Reform, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    War and Responsibility Act; Aid to Families with Dependent Children; Public Welfare; Medical Care
  - Welfare Reform, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    Public Welfare
  - WESTAR Council Conference, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    Forest Health Air Quality; Forest Reserves
    Address to WESTAR Council Conference on Forest Health and Air Quality 10/13/1994
  - Western Inland Forests, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Western Water, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    Water Resources; States Rights; Teton Dam
    H.R.649; P.L.94-100
  - Western Water Commission, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Wetland Issues, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 30)
    Wetlands; Grazing
    H.R.251; H.R.404
  - Wetlands, 1993-1994 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    National Association of Home Builders; Wetlands Protection and Management Act
    H.R.3465
  - Wetlands, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    Pheasants Forever; Environmental Protection Agency; Clean Water Act
    H.R.4416
  - Wetlands: Background, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 33)
    Clean Water Act
  - Wetlands: Federal Manual, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Wetlands: H.R.1330, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 35)
    Clean Water Act; National Association of Homebuilders
    Hays, Jimmy; Stallings, Richard
    H.R.1330
  - Wetlands: Idaho and West, 1991-1992 (Box 47, Folder 36)
    Idaho Department of Fish and Game; Idaho--Wetlands; The West--Wetlands; Wildlife Habitat
  - Wetlands: Idaho Wetlands Priority Plan, November, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 37)
    Idaho--Wetlands
  - Wetlands: Other Legislation, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 38)
    H.R.3543
  - Wetlands: Reference Materials, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - White House Conference: Aging, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Aged; Health Care Reform
  - White House Conference: Small Business, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Whitewater Investigating, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    Whitewater Investigation; Presidential Ethics
  - Wild Birds, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    Wild Bird Protection Act; National Audubon Society; World Wildlife Fund
    H.R.2540
  - Wilderness, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    Statement "Natural Resources and Wilderness in the State of Idaho" 3/9/1994
  - Wildfire Commission Report, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    Forest Fires; Forest Health
  - Wildlife Conservation: Alaska Plan, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    Alaska--Hunting; Wolves
    H.R.1391
  - Wind Energy, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    Alternative Energy Sources
  - Wolves, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    Yellowstone National Park--Wolves
  - Wolves: Background, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    Yellowstone National Park--Wolves; Central Idaho Wolf Recovery
  - Wolves: Background, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Wolves: Background, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    Wolf Recovery Foundation; Endangered Species Act; Wolves--Environmental Aspects.
  - Wolves: Background, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    Yellowstone National Park--Wolves; Central Idaho Wolf Recovery; Idaho Cattlemen's Association
  - Wolves: Background, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    Livestock
    Bangs, Ed
  - Wolves: Correspondence: Idaho Groups, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    Wolf Management; Wolves--Constituent Communication; Hunting; Defenders of Wildlife--Legal Affairs
  - Wolves: Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    Wolf Recovery Foundation
  - Wolves: Press Coverage, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    Idaho--Wolves; Yellowstone National Park--Wolves
  - Wolves: Recovery Plans, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Wolves: Yellowstone, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Women in Combat, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    Persian Gulf War; Women Soldiers
    H.R.3868
  - Women's Issues, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    American Association of University Women; National Women's Law Center; Equal Remedies Act
    H.R.3975
  - Wood Preservers, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Wool and Mohair Subsidies, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    Wool Industry; Sheep; Grazing
  - Worker Protection Standard, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    Environmental Protection Agency; Agricultural Labor
  - Workforce Security Act, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    Job Training
  - Workforce Security Act, 1994 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    Employment
  - World Banks, 1990-1991 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    World Bank; Global Arms Trade; Asian Development Bank; International Banking
    McNamara, Robert S.
  - World Energy Trends, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Yellowstone, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    Greater Yellowstone Coalition; Yellowstone National Park; Buffalo
  - Yew, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 30)
    Pacific Yew Tree; Forest Reserves
  - Yucca Mountain, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Yugoslavia, 1991-1993 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    Human Rights; Bosnia
  - Zilog, Inc., 1992 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    Nampa, Idaho
  - Zaire, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Lower Snake Reservoir Drawdown, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 35)
    Drawdowns; Salmon; Snake River; Army Corps of Engineers
- Campaigns, 2
  Larry LaRocco ran for the Idaho's 1st District seat in U.S. Congress four times. The first campaign in 1982 was against Larry Craig and was defeated. After successfully leading the drive for a state lottery in 1988, he ran again in 1990 against Skip Symser. LaRocco won with 53 percent of the vote. His announcement speech for this campaign is found in Box 1 of this series. Additional information concerning this election is in Series 4, Box 1.
  In 1992, LaRocco sought reelection, running this time against Rachel Gilbert. The folders concerning this campaign are primarily press coverage, news releases, and campaign material on both candidates. Box 1, Folder 5 highlights LaRocco's positions concerning natural resources.
  Helen Chenoweth was LaRocco's opponent in 1994. Again, natural resources dominate the debates especially the Endangered Species Act and Salmon. The files for this campaign contain a focus group study of voter issues and a position questionnaire along with general press coverage and news releases. LaRocco lost his bid for reelection by a close margin.
  - Campaign, 1990: Announcement Speech, 1990 February 15 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Announcement for Candidacy
  - Biographical Articles, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Campaign, 1992
  - Campaign, 1992: Announcement Speech (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Campaign, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Campaigns--Ethics; Campaigns--Legal Affairs
  - Campaign, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Announcement for Re-election, February 10, 1992
  - Gilbert, Rachel, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Eastman, Larry
  - Natural Resources Reference Material, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Voting; Sierra Club; Campaign, 1992; Conservation
    Hall, Bill; Gilbert, Rachel
    Listing of Bills Sponsored
  - Campaign, 1994: Announcement Speech (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Announcement for Re-election, March 31, 1994
  - Campaign, 1994: Announcement for Re-election (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Campaign, 1994: Focus Group (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Campaign, 1994--Surveys
  - Campaign, 1994: Position Questionnaires (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Campaign, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Salmon
  - Campaign, 1994: Helen Chenoweth (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Washington, DC office, 3
  The documents in Series 3 were created for in-house use by LaRocco's staff in Washington, DC, under the direction of Garry Wenske and Cherie Slayton. The papers contain material fundamental to operating a Congressional office. Box 1 comprises general files pertaining directly to LaRocco, for example biographies, personal records, and speeches. This box also contains information regarding services provided to constituents by their representatives and specific services available to members of Congress.
  Appointments became a part of the office's activities following the 1992 election. Details of LaRocco's recommendations for Idaho's federal positions are found in Box 1. The nomination of John R. Tait for U.S. District Judge of Idaho became a point of political contention in the state and in Washington, DC Material relating to Tait has been collected in Box 12.
  LaRocco's voting records are arranged by subject in Box 2 and include data received from special interest groups. Background to issues concerning Idaho is found Box 3. For example, transcripts from an oversight hearing provide insight to the controversy between the user and the conservator of western resources. Energy files directly relate to nuclear power and its waste storage.
  Legislation sponsored and cosponsored by Larry LaRocco is found in Boxes 4 and 5. Box 4 has the cosponsored bills arranged by subject while in Box 5, they are arranged by Congressional session and number. These files also contain correspondence from members of Congress requesting support on their resolutions. Form letters (ROBO's) concerning various subjects are found in Box 6. These letters were for general distribution to LaRocco's Idaho constituents.
  Specific correspondence is also found in Box 6. The files include correspondence from political colleagues, influential Idahoans, Idaho corporations, and the public. Letters classified by the staff as public relations are also in this box. General constituent requests are in Box 7.
  Representatives in Congress are provided a budget for their mail services. A record a LaRocco's frankable mail is found in boxes 8, 9, and 10. In Box 11 are the schedules of Representative LaRocco's activities during his four years in Congress.
  - Administration
    - American Legion Membership, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Personal
    - Appointments: Idaho Director, Farmers Home Administration, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Appointments: United States Attorney for Idaho, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Idaho--Attorney General
      Richardson, Betty Hansen
    - Appointments: United States Marshal for Idaho, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Benham, James H.
    - Awards, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Aged; Military
    - Biographies, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Capitol Sites, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Washington, DC
    - Caterpillar, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Public Relations
    - Caucuses Membership, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      LaRocco, Larry
    - Checklist of Congressional Record Services Products, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Commencement Addresses, 1985-1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Kamiah High School; Wendell High School; Twin Falls School
    - Committee Membership, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Computer Information, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Financial Disclosure, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Finances
    - Finances (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Graduation Speeches, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Interns and Pages, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Legislative Profile, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      Legislation
    - Newsletters Results/Reports, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Newsletters and Announcements, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Office of the Postmaster, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Congress--Postal Service
      Office
    - Office: Telephone System, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Press Releases, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Reprints for Public Distribution, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      National Rifle Association; National Guard; Drug Abuse; Child Support; Martin Luther King Day; Human Rights; Medical Care; NAFTA; Forest Reserves
      Byron, Faith
    - Staff (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Staff Assignments, 1993-94 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Cosponsorship Options, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 73)
      Medical Care; Welfare Reform Act; Community Health Improvement Act
      H.R.4024; H.R.4605
    - Cosponsorships, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 74)
      Social Security; Small Business Administration; Medical Care; Deficit Spending; Freedom of Choice Act; Education
      H.R.4475; H.R.5198; H.R.25
  - Issues
    - American Association of University Women, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Budget Tracking System, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Business Ballot, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Chamber of Commerce; Government of Business
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Children's Issues: Voting Record, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Child Support
    - Christian Coalition, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Committee for Education Funding (CEF), 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Concord Coalition, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Budget Deficit
    - Congressional Voting, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Congress--Voting
    - Consumer Federation of America, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Consumer Protection
    - Department of Agriculture, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Endangered Species Act, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Federal Housing, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Gun Control, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Home Builders, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      Construction; Housing
    - How They Voted, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - House Votes Information Services, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Independent Businesses, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - National Security, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Private Property, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      Property Owners
    - Pro-Choice, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      Abortion
    - Project Vote Smart, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Promoting Reproductive Choices, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      Planned Parenthood; Abortion
    - Public Securities Legislation, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Realtors, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      Real Estate
    - Secure Retirement, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      Retirement Income
    - Senior Citizens, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      Aged; Retirement Income; Medical Care
    - Tax-Payers Union, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      National Tax Payers Union; Voting Record
    - Tax-Payers Union, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      Taxation; Income Tax
    - Vote Ratings, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Changing Needs of the West, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      War on the West; The West-Natural Resources; Wilderness Areas
    - Changing Needs of the West, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      War on the West; The West-- Natural Resources; Wilderness areas
    - Commemorative Coin Act, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Commemorative Coins; Coinage; Persian Gulf Medal
    - Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Campaign, 1992; Democratic Party
    - Energy Bill, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Environmental Protection Act; Energy Resources
    - Energy Bill, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Energy Bill, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Energy Bill, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Everglades, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Wilderness Areas; Florida--Ecosystems
    - Everglades, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Wilderness Areas; Florida-- Ecosystems
    - Everglades, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Wilderness Areas; Florida-Eco Systems
    - Food Services, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      Morrison- Knudsen; Federal Aviation Administration
    - Idaho Parent-Teachers Association, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - International Monetary Fund: Quotas, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      International Development; Russia
    - McClure-Andrus Wilderness AreasI, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - McClure-Andrus Wilderness Areas, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Multicultural Development Bank, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      International Development
    - Northern Rockies Ecosystems, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Colorado-Ecosystems; Wilderness Areas; Water Resources
    - Payette Crest, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Idaho--Wilderness Areas; Payette National Forest
    - Resolution Trust Corporation, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Resolution Trust Corporation, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Legislation
    - Cosponsor Book: Index, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Cosponsor Book: Agriculture, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Cosponsor Book: Armed Services, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Military; Defense Department
    - Cosponsor Book: Banking, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Cosponsor Book: Education and Labor, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Labor Department
    - Cosponsor Book: Energy and Commerce, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Energy Department; Commerce Department; Solid Waste
    - Cosponsor Book: Foreign Affairs, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Cosponsor Book: Government Operations, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Cosponsor Book: House Administration, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Cosponsor Book: Interior, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Interior Department; Interior and Insular Affairs Committee
    - Cosponsor Book: Judiciary, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Justice Department
    - Cosponsor Book: Merchant Marines, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      Fisheries
    - Cosponsor Book: Post Office/Civil Service, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      Proclamations; Resolutions
    - Cosponsor Book: Public Works, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Cosponsor Book: Rules, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      China
    - Cosponsor Book: Small Business, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Cosponsor Book: Veteran's Affairs, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Cosponsor Book: Ways and Means, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      Savings and Loans; Government Spending
    - LaRocco Authored Legislation: Passed, 1991-1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Sponsored H.R. 444, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Sponsored H.R. 446, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Immigration and Nationality Act
    - Sponsored H.R. 900, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Idaho--District Judges
    - Sponsored H.R. 1845, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      National Biological Survey Act
    - Sponsored H.R. 2141, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Sponsored H.R. 2463, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Forest Reserves--Revenues; Education
    - Sponsored H.R. 2803, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Consumer Protection Act; Rental-Purchase Reform Act
    - Sponsored H.R. 3070, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Public Health Service Act; Rural Telemedicine Development Act; Medical Care
    - Sponsored H.R. 3732, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Sponsored H.R. 3909, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Rural Health Care; Public Health Service Act
    - Sponsored H.R. 4083, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      Wild and Scenic Rivers Act; Salmon River
    - Sponsored H.R. 4961, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      Coeur d'Alene Basin
    - Sponsored H.R. 4962, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Sponsored H.R. 4980, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Sponsored H.R. 229, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Sponsored H.R. 230, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Nuclear Waste
    - Sponsored H.R. 231, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Sponsored H.R. 233, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      Wild and Scenic Rivers Act
    - Sponsored H.R. 234, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      Moscow Mountains; Latah County Land Use
    - Sponsored H.R. 235, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      Idaho Land Exchange Act; Land Use
    - Sponsored H.R. 237, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      Rural Health Care
    - Coeur d'Alene Basin and Spokane River Restoration Act, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Coeur d'Alene Basin Restoration Act, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      Spokane River
    - Legislative Activity Guide Appendix, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Legislative Activity Guide 102 1st., 1991 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Legislative Activity Guide 102 1st., 1991 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Legislation, Co-Sponsored, 102nd Status, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Co-Sponsored H.R. 3-H.R. 649, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Co-Sponsored H.R. 772-H.R. 2673, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Co-Sponsored H.R. 2782-H.R. 3939, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Co-Sponsored H.R. 4011-H.R. 6062, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Legislation, Co-Sponsored Resolutions, 102nd, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Legislative Activity Guide 103 1st, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Co-Sponsored H.R.1-H.R.234, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Co-Sponsored H.R.237-H.R.846, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Co-Sponsored H.R.2575-H.R.4024, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Co-Sponsored H.R.900-H.R.1739, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Co-Sponsored H.R.1749-H.R.2345, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Co-Sponsored Joint Resolution H.J.6-1560, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Legislative Activity Guide 103 1st, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Legislation Co-Sponsored, 103rd, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Public Law 103-17, 1993 April 12 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Joint Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Joint Correspondence, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Joint Correspondence, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Public Relations
    - Correspondence: ROBO for Agriculture, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: ROBO for Animals/Wild Life, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Wolves; Endangered Species Act
    - Correspondence: ROBO for Banking, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Banksand Banking
    - Correspondence: ROBO for Budget, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Budget Deficits; Government Spending
    - Correspondence: ROBO for Campaign Issues, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      Team Limitations; Campaign, 1992
    - Correspondence: ROBO for Defense, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: ROBO for Education, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: ROBO for Energy, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Nuclear Reactors; INEL; Energy Policy
    - Correspondence: ROBO for Environment, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      Environmental Aspects
    - Correspondence: ROBO for Finance, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Finances; Davis Bacan Act